(Leonard:)No, that can't be right.
(Howard:)Maybe Thor's Hammer
is a new color of nail polish.
Then Red Hulk must be worthy!
(Penny(off):)How could Red Hulk be worthy?
(Bernadette(off):)You don't know his life.
There's only one logical explanation:
Somewhere in the desert...
(Sheldon:)...we crossed into
an alternate dimension...
(Sheldon:)...where the women in our lives
can finally appreciate great literature.
(Raj:)If it's an alternate dimension...
...that sounds like ajob
for a landing party.
(Sheldon:)Captain, what are your orders?
(Leonard:)I say we investigate.
(GPS:)Wait.
(Sheldon:)They might be hostile.
(Leonard:)Fine, but set them to stun.
(Leonard:)If we vaporize Penny, I'll never
find a girlfriend that pretty again.
(GPS:)President Eisenhower
signed the Federal Aid Highway Act...
(GPS:)...from his hospital room.
(First Car Thief:)Wow, that is interesting.
(Second Car Thief:)You learn something new every day.
Say, can you name the four state capitals
that are not served by the Interstate System?
- Ooh, another quiz?
- Yes!